inglife.co.in 2009-04-08

# Privacy Policy - ING - Life Insurance

The User specifically acknowledges that any communication transmitted by them to ING Vysya Life Insurance Company Limited (hereinafter referred to as "IVL") via the Internet may not be secure from interference or remain confidential during its transmission. IVL may be required to disclose information pursuant to applicable law, rule, regulation or such other requirements as may be in force from time to time. 

The User of this website specifically acknowledges and agrees that IVL will not be liable for any illegal and/or slanderous conduct of any person. IVL’s website sometimes requires Users to give personal information in order to do things like access webcasts, download documents, participate in online surveys, or to provide feedback. In situations like these, where Users are accessing the website, IVL recognizes Users interest in the product or service and considers that to be "opting in" to allow IVL and appropriate business partners of IVL to contact Users with information, special offers, or promotional materials in the future. IVL may transfer Users personal information to or share it with the business partner only for future marketing, development of new products, customer service, delivery of products, aftercare service and related activities thereof. If the User does not wish to be contacted, the User is requested to intimate IVL accordingly. 

IVL may also collect information in other ways, such as running quizzes, contests or any other program on IVL’s site or otherwise, in which IVL will ask the User for contact information (like postal and email address), unique identifiers (like password), and demographic information (like occupation). If User does not wish to be contacted, IVL requests that the User does not participate in these promotions.

IVL may share the information provided by the User with any other person(s) including its affiliates, business partners, re-insurers, and other third parties such as service providers. In addition, should the law or an authority require to do so, IVL may disclose any information provided by the User in the website, as required. Further, IVL will release personal information to (i) enforce or apply IVL agreements, (ii) protect IVL rights and property; and (iii) protect integrity or safety of IVL and this site.

It is specifically agreed that IVL shall be entitled to compile and analyze such information on an aggregated basis for its purposes. In pursuance of the same, IVL shall be entitled to prepare from such information such documentation, graphs or figures that it may think necessary for its purposes which may include, among others, preparation of feasibility studies, marketing or distribution methods and processes, customer lists, current and anticipated privacy requirements, commission structure, market studies, business plans, financial projections and budgets, projected profits, names and backgrounds of personnel and personnel training techniques and materials. 

This site may contain links to other sites. IVL does not control the information collection of sites that can be reached through links from this or any site controlled by IVL. If the User has questions about the data collection procedures or privacy policy of linked sites, please contact those sites directly. IVL does not undertake any responsibility for the privacy policies of the Internet service providers, partners, advertisers, and web sites that have links on this website that may collect personally identifiable information of any form from the User while accessing this or those sites through this website. 

IVL site automatically captures IP addresses. IVL uses IP addresses to help diagnose problems with IVL server, to administer IVL website, and to help ensure the security of User interaction with the website. As part of offering and providing customizable and personalized services, IVL uses cookies to store and sometimes track information about the User. A cookie is a small amount of data that is sent to the Users browser from a Web server and stored on Users computer hard drive. All sections of this site where Users are prompted to log in or that are customizable require the Users browser to accept cookies. 

The User agrees that if he/she has provided information to IVL, the same is complete, correct and accurate and IVL shall have no liability on account of the completeness, correctness or accuracy of the same.

It is the Users sole responsibility to exercise caution while deciding to disclose or key -in personal information. Due to the nature of the internet, it is possible that some other persons may be able to access or see the information that is being transmitted by the User. 

If the User has not attained 18 years of age, he/she is not encouraged to use the service or submit any personal information. Out of special concern for minor's privacy, IVL does not accept personal information from persons who are stated to be under the age of 18.

IVL reserves the right to add, amend, revise, or suspend the privacy policy from time to time.
